https://cor.org/overlandpark/operations/privacy

Church of the ResurrectionOverland ParkVisitLocationsWorship With UsOur StoryCommon QuestionsContact UsConnectChildrenStudentsCommunity & ClassesEventsStaffContact usCareRequest CarePrayerCounselingRecovery GroupsBaptismsFuneralsWeddingsServeServe OpportunitiesIn Kansas CityAround the WorldWorship OnlineResourcesSermonsGPS GuideNews & UpdatesBookstoreShareChurch & ConferencesGive2021 PledgeGive NowWays to GivePlanned Giving (Foundation)Memorial Gifts
Search
Menu
Alerts
6 months Ago Our Vision for Racial JusticeWebsite Privacy & Content Policies
Menu
Safe GatheringsCommitteesPrivacy & Content PoliciesContent PolicyAll Scripture quotations unless marked otherwise are taken from the Common English Bible ©2011, published by Abingdon Press. Used by permission. All rights reserved.All other content on this website unless marked otherwise belongs the The United Methodist Church of the Resurrection and may not be used, copied or distributed without express written permission.Privacy PolicyThis is a website of The United Methodist Church of the Resurrection headquartered in Leawood, Kansas. By using our site, you consent to our Privacy Policy as detailed below. Our website privacy policy is as follows:Information security practicesWe and our website hosting providers employ a variety of security measures in our data centers and hosting facilities to protect against the unauthorized access, theft, loss, misuse, or alteration of information we collect from you.CookiesCookies are small files that our sites store on your computer through your web browser (if you allow it) that enable our systems to recognize your browser and remember certain information. We use cookies to:Understand and save your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.Help remember and process donations or items for purchase.Compile aggregate data about site usage in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies through your browser. If you disable cookies, some of our features will not function properly.IP address trackingWhen you connect to our site, our servers recognize the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer providing you with Internet access. The IP address is used to gather location information of site visitors and can help diagnose problems with our servers or otherwise administer our site.Personal information collectionWe collect information from you when you create an account, make a donation, register for an event, sign up for a newsletter, respond to a survey, or any time you enter information into our site. Users can visit the site anonymously, with the understanding that our servers do collect IP address information.In order to complete the purposes of your visit to our site, you might be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details.We may use the information we collect from you in the following ways:To complete the purposes of your visit.To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content in which you are most interested.To improve our website in order to better serve you.To send emails regarding your account, donation, registration, etc.To send periodic email newsletters you requested.To follow up with you after correspondence with us.Third-party disclosureAny information collected is for use by the church. We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include website hosting providers and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when such release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.Access to your informationUpon request we will provide you with access to all information that we have collected about you. Visitors may obtain and correct this information by sending a request to us at info@cor.org so that we may take action to remove such information.Email from the churchIf at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can contact us at info@cor.org.Third-party linksSometimes we include or link to third-party websites on our website. Third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies; we have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.Privacy policy changesWe may change this policy from time to time. If we do, we will post the new policy here.Any questions about our website, inquiries about copyrighted material, or concerns about this policy should be directed to:The United Methodist Church of the Resurrection13720 Roe AvenueLeawood, KS 66224info@cor.org913-897-0120
Choose Your LocationLeawood
13720 Roe Ave.Leawood, KS 66224(913) 897-0120
Select
West
24000 W. Valley PkwyOlathe, KS 66061(913) 538-7800
Select
Downtown
1601 Grand Blvd.Kansas City, MO 64108(816) 979-1330
Can’t find something? Let us help.
Planned Giving (Foundation)
Memorial Gifts
Facebook
Instagram
How can we help?
Call the Overland Park Campus office at (913) 642-4400, or email using the form below.Read Common Questions
corgps-circledgps-plaingps
